[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can make Inkscape have a dark
如何才能让Inkscape拥有一片黑暗
workspace on the canvas like illustrator
画布上的工作空间，就像Illustrator
has and this is something that I've been
有，这是我一直以来
asked about a lot especially by those of
问了很多，尤其是那些
you who are switching over to Inkscape
正在切换到Inkscape的您
from Illustrator and find the glaring
从Illustrator中找到最耀眼的
white canvas of Inkscape to be somewhat
墨迹的白色画布有点
of a nuisance when you're working but
当你在工作的时候会很麻烦，但是
before we get started if you'd like to
在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
learn more about how Inkscape works be
了解有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息
sure to check out my Inkscape
一定要看看我的Inkscape
masterclass it's a collection of over 60
大师班，这是一个超过60件的收藏
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in Inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work I'll have a link in the description
工作我会在描述中有一个链接
of the video if you want to check that
如果您想要查看视频
out so to get us started here the first
所以让我们从这里开始第一次
thing you want to do is just make sure
你要做的就是确保
that you are working with the proper
您正在与适当的
version of Inkscape which is version 1.0
Inkscape的版本为1.0
or above if you don't know what your
或以上，如果您不知道您的
version is just click on help and go to
版本是只需点击帮助并转到
about Inkscape and it will tell you in
关于Inkscape，它会告诉你
this little pop-up window here as you
这里的这个小弹出窗口是您
can see I am using version 1.0 if you're
可以看到我使用的是1.0版，如果您
using 1.0 or above or greater like a
使用1.0或更高版本或更高版本
newer version then you're good to go you
更新的版本，那么你就可以走了
can close out of that if you're using an
如果您正在使用
older version like 0.9 2.5 or or
较早的版本，如0.9 2.5或或
something even older than that you'll
比那更古老的东西，你会发现
probably have to use one of my older
可能得用我的老一辈的
tutorials because what I'm going to
教程，因为我要做的是
demonstrate here won't apply to those
这里的演示不适用于那些
older versions so let's close out of
较旧的版本，所以让我们结束
that let's set the dark theme first
那就让我们先设定黑暗的主题
let's come over here to where it says
让我们到这里来，上面写着
edit and go to preferences and I'm gonna
编辑并转到首选项，我将
come over to let me close the Tools menu
过来让我关闭工具菜单
let me open up the interface menu and
让我打开界面菜单并
expand that I'm gonna click on theme I'm
展开我要点击的主题I‘m
gonna use dark theme check that and then
我要用黑暗主题检查一下，然后
use symbolic icons and check that and as
使用符号图标，然后选中并将其作为
you can see here it's already looking a
你可以在这里看到它已经看起来像一个
lot more like illustrator so let's close
更像是插图画家所以让我们结束吧
out of this menu what we want to do now
我们现在要做的不在这个菜单上
is make the workspace have a dark
就是让工作空间有一片黑暗
background here so to do that we'll get
背景，所以要做到这一点，我们将得到
a file document properties and where it
文件文档属性及其所在位置
says background color let's open that up
表示背景颜色，让我们打开它
and I'm going to choose HSL from the
我将从以下选项中选择HSL
color selector and I'm going to choose
颜色选择器和我要选择
the L row down here and just slide that
L划到这里，然后滑到那里
up and as you can see it is changing the
正如您所看到的，它正在改变
background it's changing the canvas
背景它正在改变画布
background as I change it there and I'm
当我在那里改变它的时候，我是
going to leave it right about there
我要把它放在那里
that's looking pretty good as you can
你看起来已经很不错了
see it's already a lot easier on the
你看，这已经容易得多了
eyes it isn't it isn't
眼睛，不是，不是
you don't have like this bright white
你没有像这件明亮的白色
background shining into your eyes so let
背景照进你的眼睛，所以让
me close out of that and close out of
我关闭了它，关闭了它
that what we need now is a white like a
我们现在需要的是白色的，就像
white art board to work with to do that
要做到这一点，需要与白色艺术委员会合作
let me grab the squares and rectangles
我来拿正方形和长方形
tool I'm going to create a rectangle and
我要创建一个矩形，然后
I'm going to grab the select tool let me
我要去拿选择工具让我
size this rectangle let me set the
调整此矩形的大小让我设置
increments to pixels I'm going to size
我要调整大小的像素的增量
it by 1280 by 1280 if you can size it to
1280乘以1280，如果您可以将其大小调整为
whatever you want I just like to work
无论你想要什么，我都喜欢工作
with 1280 by 1280 as a default I'm going
使用1280到1280作为默认设置，我将
to make that white and now I'm going to
让它变白，现在我要
open up the document properties again
再次打开文档属性
I'm going to file document properties
我要将文档属性归档
and over here we're looking for resized
在这里，我们正在寻找调整后的尺寸
page to content right there and resize
从页面到内容并调整大小
page to drawing or selection click on
要绘制或选择的页面，请单击
that and it's going to resize the page
然后它将调整页面的大小
boundaries around that rectangle you
你周围那个矩形的边界
have selected and where it says show
已经选择了并显示在哪里
page Bodrum is going to disable that I'd
佩奇·博德鲁姆会禁用我的
rather that not be there let's close out
宁愿不在那里，让我们结束吧
of that and as you can see we now have a
如你所见，我们现在有一个
white artboard to work with let me zoom
白色画板，让我可以放大
in on this a little bit but the problem
对此有一点了解，但问题是
you'll have now is that you can
你现在所拥有的就是你可以
accidentally click this thing and alter
不小心点击了这个东西并更改了
it while you're working it'll get your
当你工作的时候它会让你的
way so in order to anchor this thing
所以为了把这东西固定住
down what I'm going to do is use layers
下面我要做的是使用层次化
so I'll come over here to the layers
所以我会走到这一层
menu let's click on that ctrl shift and
菜单让我们点击Ctrl Shift并
L is the keyboard shortcut and I'm gonna
L是键盘快捷键，我要
rename this layer to canvas and I'm
将此层重命名为Canvas，我将
going to lock it I'm going to lock that
我要把它锁上我要把它锁上
layer so that we can't click on it and
层，这样我们就不能点击它
edit it while we're working and now I'm
在我们工作的时候编辑它，现在我
going to add a new layer on top of it
要在上面添加一个新的层
and I'm going to name this content this
我将把这些内容命名为
is the content layer click Add and there
内容图层是否单击添加，然后出现
you go now you have a set up similar to
现在，你有了一个类似于
illustrator where you have a black or a
Illustrator，你有一个黑色或一个
dark work space with a white artboard
带有白色画板的黑暗工作空间
then you can export as needed a couple
然后，您可以根据需要出口几个
of things though I'd like to point out
不过，我想指出的是
number one is Inkscape does not
第一个是Inkscape不会
recognize this white background as an
将此白色背景识别为
actual background it recognizes it as a
实际背景，它将其识别为
white rectangle so if you go to export
白色矩形，所以如果您要出口
an object on top of this background it's
在这个背景上的一个物体
going to export the white rectangle with
要使用以下命令导出白色矩形
it let me show you what I mean here if I
它让我向你们展示我这里的意思，如果我
grab the the circles and ellipses tool
抓起圆形和椭圆工具
and I click and drag to create the
然后我点击并拖动以创建
ellipse let me just make that red if I
Ellipse，让我把它变成红色，如果我
go to file export PNG image
转到文件导出PNG图像
and I exported by selection it's going
我通过选择把它出口了
to export everything within this
要导出此文件中的所有内容
rectangular bounding box including the
矩形边界框，包括
white background there because like I
白色背景，因为我喜欢
said Inkscape does not recognize this as
Said Inkscape不认为这是
a background it recognizes it as a white
一个背景，它识别出它是白色的
object so normally it would export to
对象，因此它通常会导出到
transparency here but now over this
这里是透明的，但现在是透明的
object it's going to export with the
对象，它将使用
white background to change that you can
白色背景以更改您可以
just select this option right here that
只需在此处选择此选项即可
says hide all except selected and with
表示隐藏除选定项和WITH之外的所有项
that with that selected you can now
有了那个选择，你现在就可以
export this red ellipse and get a
导出此红色椭圆并获取一个
transparent background in the corners
角落中的透明背景
here if you want to save this as your
如果您想将此文件另存为您的
startup file so that you don't have to
启动文件，这样您就不必
manually create this every time you want
每次需要时手动创建此文件
to design something just go to file save
要设计某些东西，只需转到文件保存
template and I'm going to title this
模板，我将把它命名为
dark canvas and where it says set as
深色的画布，上面写着布景
default template go ahead and check that
继续执行默认模板并检查
you know what let me get rid of this
你知道什么能让我摆脱这个吗？
right let me get rid of this ellipse
好的，让我把这个省略号去掉
first and don't want that in there let's
首先，我们不想那样做，让我们
go to file save as no I'm sorry not save
转到文件另存为否很抱歉没有保存
as save template and save this as dark
作为保存模板并将此保存为暗处理
canvas and set as default template and
画布并设置为默认模板
go ahead and click Save and what happens
继续并单击保存，然后会发生什么情况
now is you can go ahead and close out of
现在，您可以继续并关闭
Inkscape and once you reload Inkscape
Inkscape和一旦重新加载Inkscape
every time you open up Inkscape now you
每次打开Inkscape Now时，
will get this as your default template
将此作为您的默认模板
so that you don't have to do this all
这样你就不必做这一切了
the time if you don't feel like setting
如果你不想坐下来的时候
this up what I'll do is I will save this
我要做的就是把这个保存起来
document as an SVG file and I will post
文档为SVG文件，我将发布
a link to it in the description of the
的说明中有指向它的链接
video so if you want you could just
视频，如果你想要，你可以
download this file you can open it up
下载此文件，您可以打开它
with Inkscape and then just go directly
使用Inkscape，然后直接进行
to file save template and save it as
要文件保存模板并将其另存为
your default template from there so I
您的默认模板，因此我
think that should do it for this
我觉得这样就够了
tutorial that is how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
creating a a dark workspace in Inkscape
在Inkscape中创建黑暗工作区
like you would have an illustrator if
就像你会有插图画家一样，如果
you have any questions leave a comment
如果您有任何问题，请留言
below and as always thanks for watching
下面并一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]